gurucreation.com 2011-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Make Money Online

Protecting your privacy is essential and very important to us. We know that the following information will help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us on our site.

**Personal Information**  
The definition of “personal information” in context to this privacy notice refers to any information that you give out that may disclose part or your whole identity. We will only gather personal information that you decide to offer us or submit to us, such as email addresses. We are committed to our no spam policy and will not sell any information to anyone that has been collected from our visitors.

We only apply the personal information that you submit to us for their intended purposes. We do not share personally identifiable information with third party websites, organizations or other persons without your consent unless it is:

1\. Necessary to provide you with a requested service;  
2\. Lawfully authorized or required;  
3\. Or utilized in the prevention or minimization of a serious and immediate threat to a party’s health.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personal identifiable information as required by law and when we believe the disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

**Collection of Information**  
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and click Stream data. This information collected will be used to research, analyze and evaluate trends and content featured on the website, in order to improve the services to our consumers. Website traffic, that is non-identifiable by person, is used in our data collection. We may use your IP address to assist in the diagnosis and administration of our website operations. It may also be utilized in the gathering of demographic data. Occasionally, we and other websites that have been referred to may uses cookies.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal identifiable information you submit while on our website. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our website as well. We have no access to, or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers & Links.” This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. [See the “Third Party Advertisers” section.]

**Third Party Advertiser’s Links**  
Our website contain links to other sites that are not owned, operated or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each website to which we may link to, that may collect personal identifiable information. While we may use cookies in some areas of our website, cookies received with advertisements on our website are collected by the respective advertising companies, and we do not possess access to or control of such information gathered.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to these links and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your rights about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html), [here](http://www.clickbank.com/privacy.html) or [here](https://7search.com/legal/privacy.html).

**Specific Parties**  
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
——–  
* To perform the actions for which you specifically provided the information (For example, enabling us to process, validate, and verify purchases).  
* To register you as a client and establish an account for you.  
* To send you email notifications about our new or existing ClickBank products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.  
* To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.  
* To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.  
* To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.

**Your Rights**  
If your personal identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete, unsubscribe or deactivate it by emailing us on the [Contact Us](http://www.gurucreation.com/contact-us) page. In protection of the privacy of yourself and others, we may have to acquire identification before we can allow you to access information regarding yourself, in order to retrieve or change it.

**Change In Customer Privacy Policy/Statement**  
From time to time we may revise this Privacy Policy if we make material changes to the policy, we will notify you here, either by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. Please check back periodically for any updates.
